Solutions

### Our Solutions

Learn about Appcast’s enterprise solutions that are designed to meet all your talent acquisition needs.

We’re committed to solving recruitment marketing challenges for leading organizations around the globe. By combining Appcast’s award-winning programmatic tech with Bayard’s 100+ years of recruitment marketing services, we’ve doubled down on our promise.

[AppcastOne

AppcastOne transforms candidate acquisition by harnessing the power of programmatic, search, social, and traditional media into a single omni-channel enterprise solution.](https://www.appcast.io/appcast-one/)

Our Four Pillars

[Appcast Brand & Creative

Appcast Brand & Creative is a full suite of professional services from brand and strategy development to award-winning, cross-channel creatives.](https://www.appcast.io/appcast-brand-and-creative/)

###### **Why Appcast Brand & Creative?**

* Authentic brand amplification
* An industry-leading creative studio
* DEI experts
* Candidate-centric design & development

Our Approach

[What is Programmatic recruitment?

Programmatic recruitment uses software and data to efficiently find the best candidates for your open jobs.](https://www.appcast.io/what-is-programmatic-recruitment/)

[What is a Job Ad Exchange?

A job ad exchange contains thousands of job boards, sites, and sources visited by jobseekers.](https://www.appcast.io/job-ad-exchange/)

[What Role Does AI Play In Our Technology?

Find out about ‘Appcast Intelligence’ and how it takes the hard work out of filling your recruitment funnels.](https://www.appcast.io/ai-at-appcast/)  

[How is data involved?

At Appcast, data powers everything we do. Data illuminates what works, where, and why when it comes to finding the right candidates for your jobs.](https://www.appcast.io/how-is-data-involved/)

[Who we Help

We help employers across all industries cost-effectively find candidates for all their open positions, fast.](https://www.appcast.io/customers-we-help/)

[Who We Partner With

Learn about how your company can partner with Appcast to help employers hire faster and more cost-effectively.](https://www.appcast.io/partners/)

Welcome to OUR

About Us

[Our Story

Learn where we’re from and where we’re going.](https://www.appcast.io/our-story/)

[Working At Appcast

Come learn and grow alongside industry experts, amazing people, and some really sweet dogs.](https://www.appcast.io/careers/)

[News Room

Recent announcements and media coverage about Appcast.](https://www.appcast.io/news/)

[Contact Us

We’d love to connect! Reach out and we’ll get back to you as quickly as possible.](https://www.appcast.io/contact/)

##### Appcast Launches AppcastOne  

AppcastOne transforms candidate acquisition by harnessing the power of programmatic, search, social and traditional media into a single enterprise offering.

Resources

[The Library

Access treasure troves of research papers, reports, and articles to help you optimize your recruiting efforts.](https://www.appcast.io/resource-library/)

[Blog

Stay current with recruitment best practices & industry news on Appcast’s blog.](https://www.appcast.io/blog/)

[Customer Stories

Learn how our customers use programmatic recruiting to fill their hiring funnels with qualified candidates.](https://www.appcast.io/customer-stories/)

[Live & Virtual Events

Join us for upcoming live and virtual events and access past virtual events on-demand. Access our calendar here.](https://www.appcast.io/live-and-virtual-events/)

[Gender Bias Decoder

Access our new tool that highlights gender-coded terms & offers alternative wording to remove gender bias from your job ads.](https://www.appcast.io/gender-bias-decoder/)

[Recruitonomics

A destination for data-driven insights to make sense of an evolving world of work.](https://recruitonomics.com/)

Privacy Policy
==============

We take data protection seriously and have built our platform using best practices for highly secure & reliable job advertising.

### Appcast’s Privacy Policy

**Revised and Effective – April 29, 2024**

Appcast, Inc. and its subsidiary, Bayard Advertising Agency, Inc. (collectively referred to as “Appcast” or “we” or “us”) is a job advertising technology and recruitment marketing service. We also own and operate several websites (e.g., [www.appcast.io](http://www.appcast.io/ "http://www.appcast.io")).

This Privacy Policy describes (i) the types of information we collect when you use our websites (the “websites”), interact with our products, services, or applications (the “Service”) in any manner; (ii) how we use the information we collect; (iii) with whom and why we share it; and (iv) the choices we offer regarding our use of the information. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how to contact us about our privacy practices.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

We gather various types of information, including information that identifies or may identify you as an individual (“personal information”) as explained in more detail below.

**Information You Provide Us**

We receive and store personal information you submit directly to us. For example, when you register as a user of the Service, you submit basic personal information such as your name, email address, phone number, and physical address, and we collect and maintain your user ID and password, which you create and provide to us. When you fill out a hosted job application or submit your interest in certain job vacancies using a version of the Service where we host that submission process, we collect the personal information that you submit as part of that form in order to process that application, including your name, email address, physical address, and phone number.  We may also ask for your responses to employment-related questions, such as whether you know how to use certain software products, are available to work at night or have sufficient work-related permissions.  We also enable you to upload a copy of your resume or CV. We do not control what information is included in your resume or CV, but we encourage you to refrain from including sensitive personal information such as your Social Security Number, identification numbers, or financial account information.  From time to time, we may collect additional information related to your job application and prospective employment.

#### **Information Collected Through Technology**

**Through the Service**

To provide the Service, we collect certain information from job applicants using automated means, such as cookies and web beacons, when they click on an Appcast-sponsored job ad at third party websites, and when job applicants start and complete a job application at your website or a website operated by your applicant tracking system, and when certain points of the recruitment process (for example an interview or hire) have been completed. The information we collect in this manner may include IP address, browser type, device type, operating system, referring URLs, dates and times of site visits, and predictive demographic information that does not identify you individually. We anonymize IP addresses by hashing or truncating them.  A cookie is a text file that websites send to a user’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the device and browser or to store information or settings in a browser. A web beacon, also known as an Internet tag or pixel tag, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. ID syncing is a methodology for securely and privately making associations between two or more web servers about certain actions for attribution and ad optimization purposes. We may also enable third parties to use cookies, web beacons, and ID syncing to collect information when you click on an Appcast-powered job ad at third party websites, when job applicants start and complete a job application for a job vacancy, and when certain points of the recruitment process (for example an interview or hire) have been completed.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but browser settings can be changed to prevent these cookies from collecting information. Disabling cookies does not necessarily disable the use of pixel tags, web beacons and other technologies that collect information.

Unless you include it in your resume or CV, we do not collect the following information, and we urge you to exclude this information from your resume:

* Social Security Number, Driver’s License Number, or other personally identifying numbers
* Payment card information or other financial information.

**  
Through the Websites**

Our websites collect certain information related to your device automatically. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, the general location where the device is located, browser information, date and time of application or click.

**Information from Third Parties**

We may receive information about you from various third parties, such as lead generation companies, recruiters, job search websites, resumé databases, and public data sources.

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16. If you are under 16, please do not register for Appcast’s Service or send any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16, we will delete that information as soon as possible. If you believe that a child under 16 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at contact@appcast.io.

**How Do We Use the Information We Collect?**

We use the information you provide to us and the information we collect for the following purposes, in each case based on your consent, on a contract we have in place with you, or on our legitimate interest:

* Creating and managing your user account;
* Providing the Service to you, including publication of your job ads to third party sites;
* Measuring job applicants generated by Appcast-sponsored job ads;
* Responding to and communicating with you about your questions and comments;
* Providing content you request, delivering information about the Service, recommending products, and communications about us, in accordance with your marketing preferences and our Privacy Policy;
* Manage event registrations and attendance, including sending related communications to you;
* Sending you news and updates about the Service;
* Enabling you to submit a job application for an Appcast-powered job ad;
* Processing, acknowledging, and/or reminding you to complete your job application;
* Alerting you to future vacancies or other opportunities for which you may be a suitable candidate;
* Connecting you with employers;
* Operating, evaluating and improving our Service (including developing new services; managing our communications; and performing accounting, auditing, and other internal functions);
* Performing data analyses;
* Complying with applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies;
* For security purposes;
* For any other purpose about which we notify you.

#### **  
Who Do We Share Information With?**

**Vendors, Partners, and Service Providers**

We may share your information with advertising and marketing partners for purposes of publishing your job ads and with other third parties who perform services on our behalf, for example, website analytics companies (e.g., Google Analytics), and our service providers.  Our third-party advertising partners may also use these technologies to identify your browsing interests over time and across different websites to deliver targeted advertisements and other content that has been customized for you and to make predictive demographic analyses. 

**Employers**

When you click on a job advertisement, fill out a hosted job application, answer questions to indicate your interest in a job, or submit your resume in certain job vacancies using a version of the Service where we host that submission process, we will share the information you provide us with the employer to whose job you clicked on, applied to, or submitted your information for. 

**Compliance with Law and Safety**

We will access, review, preserve, and disclose the information we collect if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation, court order or other government authority; to enforce or apply our agreements; or to protect the rights, safety, and property of Appcast, Inc., its employees, affiliates, or the public. We may also cooperate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose information to the relevant agency in doing so.

**Corporate Transactions**

We reserve the right to share information in connection with any corporate transaction, including any merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of stock and/or assets, or other corporate change or financing transaction including during the course of any due diligence process or otherwise.  We may also share your information with our parent companies, subsidiaries and/or affiliates for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Failure to Provide Information**

If you do not provide certain information, this may prevent us from being able to provide you with certain Services or features, and from completing certain steps in the application, selection, and recruitment process.

**Data Storage and Security**

Information security is important to us and we use appropriate technical, organizational, and administrative security measures to protect any information we hold.  However, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. The security of your information depends on your protection of your account user IDs and passwords. Please properly select and protect your password, limit access to your computer or device, and do not disclose your user IDs or passwords to unauthorized people.

**Retention**

We will keep your personal information for as long as you use the Services, as needed to carry out the purposes we’ve described in this policy, for legitimate business purposes, and/or to comply with applicable laws.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

Privacy is an ongoing responsibility, and as such, we will update this Privacy Policy from time to time and will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. When we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we update the “Revised and Effective” date. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the Privacy Policy.  We may also notify you in other ways from time to time about the processing of your personal information.

**Do Not Track**

We adhere to the standards set out in this Privacy Policy and do not monitor or respond to Do Not Track browser requests.

**Your Responsibility Regarding Privacy Disclosures**

You are responsible for providing privacy notices to your job applicants, including notice that we are collecting certain information as described herein and any other notices required by applicable law.

**Governing Law**

This Privacy Policy and your use of the Service will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New Hampshire, without giving effect to its conflicts of law provisions. By accessing or using the Service, you consent and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the state and federal courts located in New Hampshire. A printed version of this Privacy Policy will be admissible in judicial and administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this Privacy Policy to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.

**How Can I Exercise My Data Subject Rights?**

If you would like to access, review, update, rectify, and/or delete any personal information we hold about you, or exercise any other data subject right available to you under applicable law, you can either fill out [this webform](https://appcast.io/california-consumer-privacy-act) directly or call us at **+1-800-570-5430, extension 4**. Our Privacy Team will examine your request and respond to you as quickly as possible.

You may be required to provide more information or submit proof of your identity for these requests to be processed and ensure your right to access the information (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is another appropriate security measure to ensure that personal information is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. This information will be used only for the purposes of verifying your identity and processing your request. We may not be able to comply with your request if we are unable to confirm your identity or to connect the information you submit in your request with personal information in our possession.

Please note that we may still use any aggregated and deidentified personal information that does not identify any individual, and may also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, complete transactions for which the personal information was collected, and enforce our agreements.

**Opt Out of Interest-Based Advertising**

If you prefer not to receive interest-based content and ads enabled by our advertising partners, you can object and opt out by clicking on the link [**here**](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN).

**California Privacy Notice**

The California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) imposes specific obligations on businesses processing personal information of California consumers. This California Privacy Policy supplements Appcast’s Privacy Policy and applies solely to all visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of California. This CCPA Notice does not apply to personal information that we collect from our job applicants or employees.

#### Personal Information We Collect

We may collect the following categories of personal information that you submit directly to us, through technology (such as our Service or website), or from other sources (such as our affiliates, our customers, public and publicly available sources, our service providers, our partners, and the organization with which you are employed). Personal information does not include publicly available information, de-identified or aggregated consumer information, and information excluded from the CCPA’s scope.

Identifiers, such as name, email address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, IP address, physical address, job title, user ID, and password for the Service.

Personal information categories listed in Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e), such as name, physical address, phone number, signature, address, employment history, and telephone number. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories.

Commercial Information, such as products or services purchased or considered.

Internet or other electronic network activity information, such as interactions with a website, application, or advertisement.

#### Purpose for Collecting Personal Information

We use identifiers to contact you, connect you with employers, and provide you with information.

We use identifiers and commercial information to create and manage your account and provide the Service to you.

We use internet or other electronic network activity information to operate, evaluate, and improve our Service.

**With Whom We Disclose Personal Information**

Within the preceding 12 months, Appcast has disclosed personal information as necessary for certain “business purposes,” as defined by the CCPA. This includes identifiers, personal information categories listed in Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e), commercial information, and internet or other electronic network activity with our vendors, partners and service providers.

**With Whom We Share and Sell Personal Information**

Within the preceding 12 months, Appcast has “shared” identifiers and internet or other electronic activity with third parties who perform services on our behalf, for example, website analytics companies (e.g., Google Analytics), and our advertising partners to identify your browsing interests over time and across different websites to deliver targeted advertisements and other content that has been customized for you.

Within the preceding 12 months, Appcast may have shared your personal information in ways that could be considered a “sale” under the CCPA. This includes identifiers, commercial information and internet or other electronic network activity with advertising networks, website analytics companies, and event sponsors.

#### Your Rights

Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), and subject to applicable exceptions, California consumers are entitled to the following rights:

* “Right to correct” means you have the right to request that we correct inaccurate personal information that we maintain about you.
* “Right to delete” means you have the right to request that we delete personal information about you that we have collected.
* “Right to opt-out of sale/sharing” means you have the right to request that if we sell or share personal information about you to third parties to stop doing so.
* “Right to know” means you have the right to request disclosure about what categories of personal information Appcast has sold or disclosed for a business purpose about you and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold or disclosed. Additionally, you have the right to request disclosure of specific pieces of information, such as the categories of personal information that Appcast has collected about you, the categories of sources from which Appcast collected the personal information, the business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling the personal information, the categories of third parties with whom Appcast shares personal information, the specific pieces of personal information Appcast has collected about you, the categories of personal information that Appcast disclosed about you for a business purpose, and the categories of personal information that Appcast has sold about you, as well as the categories of third parties to whom Appcast sold the information.
* “Data Portability” means you may request that we provide you with a copy of the personal information we have about you in a structured and commonly used format.
* “Right to nondiscrimination” means we will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights.

You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. Before we can process that request, we will require the authorized agent to provide us your signed permission demonstrating that they have been authorized by you to act on your behalf.

If you would like to exercise your rights, please submit a written request via [our webform](https://www.appcast.io/appcast-privacy-webform/) or contact us at **+1-800-570-5430, extension 4**. Our Privacy Team will review your request and respond to you as soon as possible.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), the United Kingdom and Gibraltar (collectively the UK), or Switzerland, please see the section below headed “Transferring Personal Data to the United States” for further information about your privacy rights.

**Transferring Personal Data to The United States**

Appcast is located in the United States. Please be aware that any information you provide to us may be transferred to, processed, or accessed in the United States and other countries in which our service providers are located, and may be subject to United States law or other international law. The privacy and data protection laws in the United States and other countries may not be equivalent to the laws in your country of residence.

When Appcast engages in such transfers of individuals in the EEA, Appcast may rely on (i) Articles 45 to 49 of the GDPR, or (ii) the EU Standard Contractual Clauses for international transfers of personal data. When Appcast engages in such transfers of individuals in the UK, Appcast may rely on (i) Articles 45,46 or 49 of the UK GDPR and Section 17A of the Data Protection Act 2018, or (ii) the EU Standard Contractual Clauses, as amended by the UK International Data Transfer Addendum to the EU Standard Contractual Clauses. When Appcast engages in such transfers of individuals in Switzerland, Appcast may rely on the EU Standard Contractual Clauses, as amended by the Swiss Addendum to the EU Standard Contractual Clauses. In particular, Appcast collects and transfers outside the EEA and UK personal data only: with your consent, to perform a contract with you, or to fulfill a legitimate interest of Appcast in a manner that does not outweigh your rights and freedoms. Appcast endeavors to apply suitable safeguards to protect the privacy and security of your personal data and to use it only consistent with your relationship with Appcast and the practices described in this Privacy Policy.  We acknowledge our liability for such data transfers to third parties.

We will always give you an opportunity to choose opt out before your personal data is (1) disclosed to a third party (other than an agent doing work at our direction), or (2) to be used for a purpose that is materially different than that for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you. The only exception to this choice would be where we are required to disclose your personal data pursuant to government or judicial order, law, or regulation to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Appcast complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce.  Appcast has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union and the United Kingdom in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF.  Appcast has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF.  If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the DPF program, and to view our certification, please visit  [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/)

In compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, Appcast commits to resolve DPF Principles-related complaints about our collection and use of your personal information. EU, UK, and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our handling of personal data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF or the Swiss-U.S. DPF should first contact us at [dpo@appcast.io](mailto:dpo@appcast.io) or at 1-800-570-5430, extension 4. We will investigate your complaint, take appropriate action, and report back to you within 45 days.

If you are not satisfied with our response, Appcast, Inc. has agreed to participate in the dispute resolution procedures in compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF. Appcast commits to cooperate and comply respectively with the advice of the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs), the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) and the Gibraltar Regulatory Authority (GRA), and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) with regard to unresolved complaints concerning our handling of personal data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF, and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF.

Finally, as a last resort and in limited situations, EU, UK, and Swiss individuals may invoke binding Data Privacy Framework arbitration. To learn more about this mechanism and your eligibility, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf?tabset-35584=2](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf?tabset-35584=2%22%20\t%20%22_blank)

The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Appcast’ s compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF.

**EU Representative**

Appcast has appointed its parent company, Stepstone GmbH, as its representative in the EU for data protection matters.  In addition to Appcast, you may contact our Data Protection Officer on all issues related to our processing of personal data via email at [heiner.tent@stepstone.com](mailto:heiner.tent@stepstone.com) or via mail at Stepstone GmbH, Mr. Heiner Tent, Völklinger Str. 1, 40219 Düsseldorf, Germany.

**Enforceability; Non-waiver**

In the event that any provision of this Privacy Policy conflicts with applicable law, rule, regulation or order or if any provision is held invalid by a court with competent jurisdiction, then such provision will be deemed to be restated to reflect as nearly as possible our original intentions, and the remainder of this Privacy Policy will remain in full force and effect. Any failure by us to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of the Privacy Policy or to exercise any right under the Privacy Policy will not be construed as a waiver or relinquishment of our right to assert or rely upon any such provision or right in that or any other instance, rather, the same will be and remain in full force and effect.

**Contact**

If you want to reach our Privacy Team or you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or your personal data, please contact us at **+1-800-570-5430, extension 4** or via [our webform](https://www.appcast.io/appcast-privacy-webform/).

**Appcast Headquarters:  
10 Water Street  
Lebanon, NH, 03766, USA**

We’re celebrating our 10th anniversary. A decade of award-winning programmatic job advertising technology.

Keep up to date with all the latest from Appcast:

get in touch

* [1 (800) 570-5430](tel:%201%20(800)%20570-5430)

partners

* [Do not sell or share my  
    personal information](https://www.appcast.io/appcast-privacy-webform/)

© 2024 Appcast All Rights Reserved
